[Music]
[Applause]
I guess she just wasn't hearing me you
know what I mean yeah sure like we were
definitely communicating but I think at
the time I didn't realize that it are
you
listening yeah you you said your mom was
um listening what are you writing just
like reminders and like a to-do list
kind of a thing okay can you just that's
actually private so if you could just W
this every day not every day but most
are these all dreams some are dreams but
it's not all dreams so I'm running
through a field every step sounds like a
cowo I being stopped by my seventh grade
English teacher Mr wish Ley dressed like
one of those British guards that don't
move and he tells me the plot of home
alone while he rubs butter on a globe
the globe is actual size he is thirsty I
am thirsty I wake
up just give it back please oh here's
another one uh I'm sewing a patchwork
quilt out of a thousand photos of
Charlie o and winning tickets in an
arcade on a cruise ship all the lights
are
sounds I find a bucket of tickets on the
floor the tickets are sand the prizes
are sand the ocean crashes into the sand
all of the sand sand gorlock is sand he
is thirsty I am thirsty I wake up do all
of these end the same way are you just
dehydrated
no I don't know yes the ocean crashed
into the tickets into the bucket
it what the ocean crashed into the
bucket which then extended outward to
become the whole ground so it became the
beach a single bucket became the whole
Beach we were still at the arcade but
like the bucket had become the whole
ground now like the walls of the arcade
were still like can you just I don't
want to give it back this one isn't a
dream okay here we have a list entitled
list of goals as it's very old it's
maybe a month old one learn Spanish two
find Bridget three see Patrick's hat D
we're doing letters now D figure out the
year e appease gorlock who is
gorlock I don't want to like it
doesn't Okay um you know how when you
close your eyes and when you close your
eyes you can see like blotches of
light yeah and you know like if you keep
your eyes closed long enough those
blotches
like form a
face uh and you know how that face like
demands certain things and has like
certain
expectations just I'm not I was in the
in the middle of writing so I don't it's
not really a good sharing
moment you just need to drink the water
I don't want to it tastes like
wires
run
okay should we just grab some
[Music]
stuff